Chen He

Front-end Developer

0451 699 387

chenhe.elec@gmail.com

https://github.com/chenhe-henry

www.linkedin.com/in/chenhe-henry

https://chenhe-henry.github.io/myportfolio/

Profile

I'm a front-end developer with a background in electrical and electronic engineering. With over two years' experience as a technical executive, I have killer attention to detail, which means I see issues arising more quickly than others. With the proven ability as a critical thinker, I'm able to devise effective and efficient workflows. To become more creative and to explore my ability to turn people's wonderful ideas into reality, I decided to move into software engineering, the industry with a lifetime of exciting challenges.

Education

General Assembly Software Engineering Immersive Aug 2019 – Feb 2020

University of New South Wales Master of Engineering Science Jul 2014 – Dec 2016

Key Skills

HTML/CSS/JavaScript

SASS/SCSS

Responsive Design

jQuery

Bootstrap

Ruby on Rails

React.js

Vue.js

GitHub/Bitbucket

Heroku/Netlify

Express.js

Node.js

SQL/Postgres

MongoDB

Amazon Web Services (AWS)

Experience

Volunteer Web Developer

Cody.Sydney

June 2020 - Present

- Build projects with Vue.js.
- Code reviewer, provide comments to other developers' pull request.

Software Engineer Intern

Skilligi

June 2020 - Present

- Responsible for assisting and writing code using JavaScript, Node.js, SCSS, and Ruby on Rails.
- Build WordPress website with Themes, Elementor, and Plugins.
- Provide documentation about workflow, and trouble-shooting process.
- Collaborate with team members via Bitbucket and Airtable.

Software Engineering Immersive Program

General Assembly

Aug 2019 – Feb 2020

A 24-week intensive full-stack bootcamp, which covers languages, frameworks and modern technical tools include HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Ruby on Rails, SQL/Postgres, Heroku, React.js, Express, Node.js and MongoDB etc.

During the period of the program, I completed a number of practical projects:

 Project – "Portfolio", a multi-page portfolio, keep learning and growing new skills, continuously refactor with new techs. Created with Vue.js, HTML/SCSS, deployed on GitHub pages, applied responsive design, and tested accessibility with Lighthouse.

Live link: https://chenhe-henry.github.io/myportfolio/

 Project - "Find Home", a web app allows you to login with Google account, search and get details of properties for rental. Created with React.js, Express,

Languages

English

Chinese

Certifications

ITIL Foundation Level
AWS Certified Solutions
Architect – Associate

Volunteer

Code.Sydney – Web Developer Node.js, MongoDB, Mongoose, Google OAuth, Domain API, and Google Map API. Deployed on Heroku.

Live link: https://findhome101.herokuapp.com/

 Project – "Health Tracking", a health tracking system which allows you to record your health data, and calculate your BMI (body mass index) to have an overview of your health condition. Created with HTML, CSS, Vue.js. Deployed on GitHub page.

Live link: https://chenhe-henry.github.io/health-tracking/

 Project - "To Do List", a simple web application, which allows you to add, edit, delete, highlight, check and search "todos". Created with HTML, CSS, Bootstrap and jQuery.

Live link: https://chenhe-henry.github.io/gaseifx01-project0/

Technical Executive
HiTV Communications Pty.Ltd
Apr 2017 – Dec 2019

- This company provides in-car electronic devices for dealer all over Australia. I'm solely responsible for providing technical support, including issue diagnoses, analyzing and rectify for "Navigation system" and "DVR system".
- Deliver comprehensive test reports and user guides which over 400 pages.
- Devise effective and efficient processes/workflows which over 200 pages, successfully achieve 5 times more efficient on production.
- Proven ability to undertake multi-task and work under pressure, always setup and customize products for different companies within urgent due day.
- Good team player with communication and corporation skills.